<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="help_title">HOW TO PLAY</string>
    <string name="help_one">1. <b>AIM OF THE GAME</b>\nThe aim of the game is to guess accurately(in letter and position) a set
    of letters chosen from a pool of a larger number of letters. The
    number of characters to be guessed depends on the game difficulty selected\n
    4 for 4killed\n5 for 5killed;and\n6 for 6killed\n</string>
    <string name="help_two">2. <b>THE POOL AND KEYPAD</b>\nThe pool is the larger number of letters referred to in 1 where the letters to
    be guessed are selected from. The keypad in the game screen shows all the letters
    contained in the pool</string>

    <string name="help_three">3. <b>SPECIAL ALPHAS</b>\nThe computer picks a certain number of letters(depending on game difficulty)
    on game start from the pool and keeps these selected letters hidden through out the
    session of the game. These letters are referred to as <b><i>SPECIAL ALPHAS</i></b>. These letters
    do not change through out the session of the game.</string>

    <string name="help_four">4. <b>GAME START</b>\nCounter starts counting and the special alphas are picked.</string>

    <string name="help_five">5. <b>MAKE A GUESS</b>\nClick on a letter on the keypad to add that letter to the input. When the inputs
    are full, click on the submit button to make a guess</string>

    <string name="help_six">6. <b>DISPLAY AND RESULT</b>\nAfter submitting the screen is updated with your guess on the left and result on the
    right. The result appears in form of \'nk ni nn\'</string>

    <string name="help_seven">7. <b><i>k</i> KILLED</b>\nThe \'k\' in \'nk\' as displayed in the result stands for killed. This means
    \'n\' letters were guessed correctly. 4killed for example,let special alphas be \'ASDF\'
    and let your guess be \'BSUF\', \'S\' and \'F\' were guessed correctly in both letter and position
    therefore the result will be in form \'2k ni nn\'</string>

    <string name="help_eight">8. <b><i>i</i> INJURED</b>\nThe \'i\' in \'ni\' as displayed in the result stands for INJURED. This means
    \'n\' letters were guessed correctly but their postions are guessed wrongly.
    4killed for example,let special alphas be \'ASDF\'
    and let your guess be \'SBUF\', \'S\' and \'F\' were guessed correctly in letter but the postion of
    \'S\' in the guess does not match that of the special alphas. Therefore the result will be in
    the form \'1k 1i nn\'</string>

    <string name="help_nine">9. <b><i>n</i> NONE</b>\nThe \'n\' in \'nn\' as displayed in the result stands for NONE. This means
    \'n\' letters in the guess are not present in the special alphas.
    4killed for example,let special alphas be \'ASDF\'
    and let your guess be \'SBUF\', \'B\' and \'U\' are not contained in the special alphas
    .Therefore the result will be in the form \'1k 1i 2n\'</string>

</resources>